Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers, 1931-2014 MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Non-commercially Released Media, 267152
  - Subseries B: Video recordings, 269261
    - "Montano: Segal '97", 1997; ID: 386.0375; 270723 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0375)
      "Hyde Park"
    - "Montano Slides", undated; ID: 386.0376; 270773 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0376)
    - "Mother: Fairy Tale", undated; ID: 386.0377; 270914 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0377)
    - "Mother Teresa plus Fairy Tale", 2010; ID: 386.0378; 270960 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0378)
      "Version 3"
    - "Movie About Flowers", undated; ID: 386.0379; 270834 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0379)
      "Scientific; 24 min."
    - "My Little Pony in E.P.", undated; ID: 386.0380; 270838 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0380)
      "44 min."
    - "My Pope Dream", August 14, 2013; ID: 386.0381; 270970 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0381)
      "14:08 min."
    - "Nadia Grozlovow", undated; ID: 386.0382; 270858 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0382)
      "500 Hoola"
    - "Nurse! Nurse!: No Time Code", March 26, 2013; ID: 386.0383; 270969 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0383)
    - "Oak Harbor", undated; ID: 386.0384; 270958 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0384)
    - "Oh Say Can You See: Dub", 1978; ID: 386.0385; 270888 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0385)
      "Linda Montano (1978) Dub. 'Stay Tuned' Exhibition, New Museum 7/81"
    - "On Death and Dying" Linda Montano, 1982; ID: 386.0386; 270683 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0386)
      "22 min. The Art Institute of Chicago"
    - "On Death and Dying: Master Edit", November 1982; ID: 386.0387; 270746 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0387)
      "Recorded live on Ch. 6 Woodstock. Color. 22 minutes."
    - "Passion of Joan of Arc", undated; ID: 386.0388; 270835 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0388)
    - "Pauline Oliveros", May 9, 1979; ID: 386.0389; 270894 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0389)
      "Music Track only. Dub I color. 'I met Pauline Oliveros in March, 1975 and have documented the relationship in many ways for these 5 years. It fascinates me to think that we were all infants, or 11 years old or rode horses at amusement parks as children. When I found old photographs of Pauline I was able to visually observe the history of her life. Yes, even Pauline Oliveros was once five....' -Linda Montano."
    - "Pauline Oliveros: Music and Voice", undated; ID: 386.0390; 270895 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0390)
      "Original; color."
    - "Pe.A.Ch.: 337C: Topics May Vary: A Tribute to Linda Montano", October 9, 1997; ID: 386.0391; 270867 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0391)
      "[PErformance Art CHurch] Hosts: Olivia Aldin, S. Alton Dulaney, Tiana Hux. Music: Graham Reynolds and Kim Hill"
    - "People at CME", May 25, 1978; ID: 386.0392; 270887 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0392)
      "Marsha, Debbie, Phil, Rob, Linda, Terri, Albert, Ed, Jean Charles, Pauline, David, Roger, Richard, Joan, Bruce R., Glyn, Bruce L., Linda."
    - "Performance Class: Soap Operas", undated; ID: 386.0393; 270890 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0393)
      "Chicago"
    - "Pool Performance", February 19, 1988; ID: 386.0394; 270886 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0394)
      "Camera: Michael A. Lucas. OSU '88."
    - "Pre-Thesis Performance #4" Manda Barbour, undated; ID: 386.0395; 270805 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0395)
    - "Pre-Thesis Performance #5" Manda Barbour, undated; ID: 386.0396; 270806 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0396)
    - "Primal Scenes", 2004; ID: 386.0397; 270899 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0397)
      "10 min."
    - "Primal Scenes: Dub II", March 17, 1980; ID: 386.0398; 270902 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0398)
    - "R Bjerum - Original", undated; ID: 386.0399; 270732 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0399)
      "Cancer/Bed/Money; Jaiiv Song with Ganesh/Shiva Parvatii; L. Montano '95"
    - "Raw Footage of Girls Dancing and Waving", 1998; ID: 386.0400; 270836 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0400)
    - "Rejuvenation + AIDS" Dr. Mehta, April 1991; ID: 386.0401; 270844 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0401)
    - "Relationships", December 1982; ID: 386.0402; 270743 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0402)
      "Color; 14 minutes. Heart w/VIcky [Sterup], [Ellen] Cross, Montano as Heart Specialist."
    - "Response to Linda Weintraub's Oberlin Artists" Linda Montano, October 31, 2000; ID: 386.0403; 270671 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0403)
      "Halloween Day"
    - "Rites of Passion", undated; ID: 386.0404; 270869 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0404)
    - "Rope Piece: High Performance", undated; ID: 386.0405; 270865 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0405)
      "Linda Montano and Tehching Hsieh: Master; approx. 16 mins."
    - "Rose Song", undated; ID: 386.0406; 270739 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0406)
      "Rose Song with Oliveros; 10 min."
    - "Sachicoism 3", September 1981; ID: 386.0407; 270804 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0407)
      Originally under Montano's label "Sachicoism: Kioki, Japan"
      "28 minutes. Directed by Keisuke Oki 2-27-9. Megurohoncho, Meguro-ku, Tokyo/52. Japan"
    - "Sacred Sex", undated; ID: 386.0408; 270873 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0408)
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Complete", undated; ID: 386.0409; 270669 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0409)
      Originally under Montano's label "Teresa of Avila."
      "Linda Montano; 3"
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Footage not used for T of Avila", undated; ID: 386.0410; 270665 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0410)
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Revised", June 25, 2007; ID: 386.0411; 270666 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0411)
      "By Linda Mary Montano; 38 minutes"
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: 2nd to Last Edit", undated; ID: 386.0412; 270668 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0412)
      "2nd to Last Edit not 2 bad; a John St."
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Time Code", March 29, 2007; ID: 386.0413; 270667 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0413)
      "37 minutes"
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Work Tape 1", undated; ID: 386.0414; 270663 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0414)
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Work Tape 2", undated; ID: 386.0415; 270664 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0415)
    - "St. Teresa Working Tape", undated; ID: 386.0416; 270924 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0416)
      "36 min."
    - "St. Teresa Working Tape 1", undated; ID: 386.0417; 270921 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0417)
      "Rosary beads, Communion, baby, tube in nose"
    - "St. Teresa Working Tape 2", undated; ID: 386.0418; 270922 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0418)
      "Nun, Nose, Kids Wave. 8 min."
    - "St. Teresa Working Tape 3", undated; ID: 386.0419; 270923 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0419)
      "Accupuncture, Sky. 40 min."
    - "Seven Chakras: Time Code Test", August 12, 2011; ID: 386.0420; 270973 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0420)
    - "The Seven Lives of Linda Montano: Original Source Footage", undated; ID: 386.0421; 270930 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0421)
    - "The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", April 12, 1996; ID: 386.0422; 270777 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0422)
      "TRT: 12:49"
    - "Seven Stages of Intoxication", April 26, 1995; ID: 386.0478; 271062 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0478)
      Duration: 34 min.
    - "Seven Stages of Intoxication: Edited Master", April 26, 1995; ID: 386.0423; 270748 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0423)
      "Stereo; TRT: 34:00"
    - "Seven Stages of Intoxication: Original Raw Footage Unedited", undated; ID: 386.0424; 270751 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0424)
    - "Seven Years: 1st Cut", undated; ID: 386.0425; 270871 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0425)
      "Maida Barbour"
    - "Seven Years of Living Art", undated; ID: 386.0426; 270749 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0426)
      "Producer: Maida Barbour; Running Time: 13:03"
    - "Seven Years of Living Art", undated; ID: 386.0427; 270791 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0427)
      "Producer: Maida Barbour. Running Time: 13:03"
    - "Seven Years of Living Art", undated; ID: 386.0428; 270870 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0428)
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0429; 270790 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0429)
      "Linda M. Montano..'Seven Years of Living Art' Producer: Maida Barbour; 'Seven Stages of Intoxication' Linda M. Montano with Andy Cochrun and Chris Erlon; 'The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna' Linda M. Montano with Andy Cochrun and Chris Erlon; 'The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano' Linda M. Montano with Andy Cochrun and Chris Erlon"
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, and The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0430; 270740 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0430)
      Originally under Montano's label "Compilation/Working Tapes."
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0431; 270741 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0431)
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0432; 270854 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0432)
      Originally under Montano's label "Compilation Video and Audio."
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0433; 270881 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0433)
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0434; 270882 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0434)
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0435; 270883 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0435)
    - "Seven Years: Rough Edit Dub", undated; ID: 386.0436; 270880 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0436)
    - "Sex", undated; ID: 386.0437; 270904 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0437)
    - "Sex: 3 kinds", 1980; ID: 386.0438; 270901 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0438)
      "Master Tape"
    - "Sex: From Annie Sprinkle", undated; ID: 386.0349; 270897 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0349)
      "Slow Motion Time"
    - "Sex One/Sex Two" Montano/Kolpan, 1986; ID: 386.0440; 270903 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0440)
      "32 minutes, 3/4" Master"
    - "Sister Jacques", September 10, 1981; ID: 386.0441; 270885 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0441)
    - "Sister Jacques Bernadette on The Live! Show", January 28, 1983; ID: 386.0442; 270857 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0442)
    - "Sister Jacques Edit: 7th and Summary Chakra", 1982; ID: 386.0443; 270861 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0443)
    - "Sister Jacques Edit: First 6 Chakras", undated; ID: 386.0444; 270862 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0444)
      "Master Edit"
    - "Sister Rose", undated; ID: 386.0445; 270860 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0445)
      "2nd is good"
    - "Sister Rose, Anorexia, Sister Jacques (4th Chakra), The End Is Near", undated; ID: 386.0446; 270755 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0446)
      "49:45, color."
    - "Sister Speaks: About Tenure, About the Priesthood, About Talking Nicely" Linda Montano, 1999; ID: 386.0447; 270726 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0447)
    - "Sister Speaks: About Tenure, About the Priesthood, About Talking Nicely" Linda Montano, 1999; ID: 386.0448; 270727 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0448)
    - "Spring '99 Work Sampler" Lara Davis, 1999; ID: 386.0449; 270876 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0449)
    - "Sprinkle PPM", undated; ID: 386.0450; 270866 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0450)
    - "The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna", undated; ID: 386.0451; 270792 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0451)
      "23:00"
    - "The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna: Raw Footage", undated; ID: 386.0452; 270747 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0452)
    - "Tarot at New Museum", undated; ID: 386.0453; 270680 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0453)
      "Transferred from H8mm"
    - "Television Appearances about Exorcism" Father James LeBar, undated; ID: 386.0454; 270978 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0454)
    - "Thank You Mrs. Mehta: Time Code", July 7, 2010; ID: 386.0455; 270971 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0455)
      "38 minutes"
    - "The Three of Me" Edna Floretta, undated; ID: 386.0456; 270956 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0456)
    - "Three Statements After September 11; Fairytale/Lifeists/Chakra Prayer", undated; ID: 386.0457; 270672 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0457)
      "3 Statements After 9/11: 1) Fairytale, 2) Lifeists/Artists, 3) Chakra/Sacrament Prayers"
    - "The Trial of the Sands of Time" Helene Aylon, 1989; ID: 386.0458; 270874 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0458)
      "22 Minutes. Documentation: Myriam Abramowicz. with Linda Montano, Betty Parsons, Susan Griffin, Pauline Oliveros, Anna Halprin, Moira Roth, Peter Selz, Jim Melchert, Marc Kasky, Charles Shere, Myriam Abramowicz, Maryel Norris."
    - "Tones / Teresa", undated; ID: 386.0459; 270927 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0459)
    - "Two Aryuvedic Doctors", November 11, 2009; ID: 386.0461; 270975 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0461)
      "44 minutes"
    - "Two Aryuvedic Doctors", October 6, 2009; ID: 386.0460; 270965 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0460)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors", undated; ID: 386.0462; 270793 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0462)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors", undated; ID: 386.0463; 270840 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0463)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors", undated; ID: 386.0464; 270841 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0464)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors", undated; ID: 386.0465; 270842 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0465)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors: Midwife Interview Dr. A.L. Mehta", undated; ID: 386.0466; 270843 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0466)
    - "Valentine's Day", 1997; ID: 386.0467; 270934 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0467)
    - "Vivekananda: Healing" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0468; 270731 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0468)
    - "Where the Deer and Antelope Play", undated; ID: 386.0469; 270884 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0469)
      "Music (mixed) - Ch.1"
    - "Why I am Not at Western Front", February 14, 2003; ID: 386.0470; 270695 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0470)
      "Linda Montano Video; 4"
    - "Why I'm Not at Your Birthday Party", August 2003; ID: 386.0471; 270715 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0471)
      "Malcha"
    - "Workshop Tuesday Performance: Nina and Garden", undated; ID: 386.0472; 270909 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0472)
      "for Rose"
  - Subseries C: Films, 269262
    - "Linda M. Montano: 11-22-93", November 22, 1993; ID: 386.0473; 270947 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0473)
      Original format: 8mm film.
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.0474; 270944 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0474)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.0475; 270945 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0475)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.0476; 270946 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0476)
- Series VIII: Data Storage, 267887
  This series contains DVD-R, CD-R, and floppy discs, primarily related to work on Montano's books. Related paper material can be found in Series I, Subseries B.
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - 2 Professional, Legal Contracts, ID: 386.3.0001; 271023 (Box 70, Folder 1, Media ID: 386.3.0001)
    Original format: 3 floppy discs.
  - 3 Interviews, undated; ID: 386.3.0002; 271024 (Box 70, Folder 2, Media ID: 386.3.0002)
  - 4 Catholic Information, undated; ID: 386.3.0003; 271025 (Box 70, Folder 3, Media ID: 386.3.0003)
    Original format: 4 floppy discs.
  - 5 Plays, undated; ID: 386.3.0004; 271026 (Box 70, Folder 4, Media ID: 386.3.0004)
    Original format: 1 floppy disc.
  - 5 Writings, undated; ID: 386.3.0005; 271027 (Box 70, Folder 5, Media ID: 386.3.0005)
  - 6 A Performance, undated; ID: 386.3.0006; 271028 (Box 70, Folder 6, Media ID: 386.3.0006)
  - 7A Dad Art, undated; ID: 386.3.0007; 271029 (Box 70, Folder 7, Media ID: 386.3.0007)
  - 8 Reprint of Art in Everyday Life, undated; ID: 386.3.0008; 271030 (Box 70, Folder 8, Media ID: 386.3.0008)
  - 9 Letters of Linda M. Montano, undated; ID: 386.3.0009; 271031 (Box 70, Folder 9, Media ID: 386.3.0009)
  - 10 Misc. "Forget This Seems to be Jennie Sorkin Stuff", undated; ID: 386.3.0010; 271032 (Box 70, Folder 10, Media ID: 386.3.0010)
  - Academia Deconst. Tenure, undated; ID: 386.3.0011; 271033 (Box 70, Folder 11, Media ID: 386.3.0011)
  - Angelika Festa: Shall We Talk?, 1997-1998; ID: 386.3.0012; 271034 (Box 70, Folder 12, Media ID: 386.3.0012)
  - Copulating Couple for LOVE SEX, undated; ID: 386.3.0013; 271035 (Box 70, Folder 13, Media ID: 386.3.0013)
    Original format: 2 floppy discs.
  - Email, undated; ID: 386.3.0014; 271036 (Box 70, Folder 14, Media ID: 386.3.0014)
  - Food, Sex, Money, Death LM Resume, undated; ID: 386.3.0015; 271037 (Box 70, Folder 15, Media ID: 386.3.0015)
  - Food Sex Money Death, Mill 1, May 1992; ID: 386.3.0016; 271053 (Box 70, Folder 16, Media ID: 386.3.0016)
  - Friends Forever: The NY Reunion, September 2002; ID: 386.3.0017; 271057 (Box 70, Folder 17, Media ID: 386.3.0017)
    Original format: CD-R.
  - Jennifer Howard Grad School, undated; ID: 386.3.0018; 271038 (Box 70, Folder 18, Media ID: 386.3.0018)
  - Laura Cottingham "Fame & Money", undated; ID: 386.3.0019; 271039 (Box 70, Folder 19, Media ID: 386.3.0019)
  - Linda, undated; ID: 386.3.0020; 271040 (Box 70, Folder 20, Media ID: 386.3.0020)
  - Linda Intro by Annie Sprinkle, undated; ID: 386.3.0021; 271041 (Box 70, Folder 21, Media ID: 386.3.0021)
  - Linda Montano.doc from Kara Reilly NYU, undated; ID: 386.3.0022; 271042 (Box 70, Folder 22, Media ID: 386.3.0022)
  - Linda M. Montano Gentle At Last Performance Documentation, October 2006; ID: 386.3.0023; 271043 (Box 70, Folder 23, Media ID: 386.3.0023)
  - Linda Release, undated; ID: 386.3.0024; 271044 (Box 70, Folder 24, Media ID: 386.3.0024)
  - Linda Resume, etc., undated; ID: 386.3.0025; 271054 (Box 70, Folder 25, Media ID: 386.3.0025)
  - Montano Book, undated; ID: 386.3.0026; 271045 (Box 70, Folder 26, Media ID: 386.3.0026)
    Original format: 2 Zip 100.
  - Neil Graduation Madison Birthday, May 24, 2001; ID: 386.3.0027; 271046 (Box 70, Folder 27, Media ID: 386.3.0027)
  - Peter Ketter's Recommendation Letter, undated; ID: 386.3.0028; 271055 (Box 70, Folder 28, Media ID: 386.3.0028)
  - Photos, undated; ID: 386.3.0029; 271047 (Box 70, Folder 29, Media ID: 386.3.0029)
  - [Moira] Roth/Food Intro + Bio, March 1998; ID: 386.3.0030; 271048 (Box 70, Folder 30, Media ID: 386.3.0030)
  - Sheelah Murthy MFA, undated; ID: 386.3.0031; 271056 (Box 70, Folder 31, Media ID: 386.3.0031)
  - Transmedia, undated; ID: 386.3.0032; 271049 (Box 70, Folder 32, Media ID: 386.3.0032)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.3.0033; 271050 (Box 70, Folder 33, Media ID: 386.3.0033)
    Original format: 1 CD-R; 1 floppy disc.
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.3.0034; 271059 (Box 70, Folder 34, Media ID: 386.3.0034)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.3.0035; 271060 (Box 70, Folder 35, Media ID: 386.3.0035)
  - "What Kind of Software Was Used to Create This", 1992-1998; ID: 386.3.0036; 271051 (Box 70, Folder 36, Media ID: 386.3.0036)
  - Writings 1-10 as seen in Brown Book, 2007; ID: 386.3.0037; 271052 (Box 70, Folder 37, Media ID: 386.3.0037)
  - Writings by Edna Floretta, undated; ID: 386.3.0038; 271058 (Box 70, Folder 38, Media ID: 386.3.0038)
- Series IX: Objects, 267153
  This series consists of objects that were made by or belonged to Montano. The objects are arranged to reflect the overall arrangement of the collection.
  These objects are arranged to reflect the overall series order.
  - Linda Montano Keychain, undated; 268905 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0001)
  - Linda Montano Keychain: "For a Thrill Look...", undated; 268907 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0003)
  - Seven Years of Living Art/Seven Chakras framed miniature portraits, undated; 274344 (Box 83, Object ID: 386.2.0028)
  - LOVESICK Barsoap, undated; 268908 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0004)
  - "My Way of Life Pocket Edition of St. Thomas", undated; 268910 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0006)
  - "Daily Missal of the Mystical Body", November 16, 1956; 268911 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0007)
  - Holy Bible from Dr. Mehta, December 25, 1994; 268912 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0008)
  - "The Liber Usualis", 1959; 268913 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0009)
  - Montano Performance Piece: Word Association, undated; 268914 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0010)
  - "Photo-a-day by Linda Montano" Kodak case, 1974; 268915 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0011)
  - Woodcut Form 1, undated; 268927 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0023)
  - Woodcut Form 2, undated; 268928 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0024)
  - Woodcut Form 3, undated; 268929 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0025)
  - Woodcut Form 4, undated; 268930 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0026)
  - Annie Sprinkle ceramic bowl in velvet bag, January 1, 1995; 268923 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0019)
  - "Annie Sprinkle's Post-Modern Pin-Ups: Pleasure Activist Playing Cards", undated; 268906 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0002)
  - Annie Sprinkle purple barrette, undated; 268922 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0018)
  - Tehching Hsieh's wallet, undated; 268909 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0005)
  - Small figure in plastic rectangle, 1998; 268916 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0012)
  - Small yellow ceramic dog head, undated; 268917 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0013)
  - Ceramic clock and fork by R. Howland, 1986; 268918 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0014)
  - Henry J. Montano Bank Plaque, February 1969; 268919 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0015)
  - Subscription Opus Issue 18: Jude Weirmeir, undated; 268920 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0016)
  - Red cotton dinner napkin puppet, February 1998; 268921 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0017)
  - "A Bag Book" by Betsy Damon, February 9, 1983; 268924 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0020)
  - Eraser performance art piece, undated; 268925 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0021)
  - "The Perpetual Napkin" by Barbara Smith, 1981; 268926 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0022)
  - Hannah Wilke Gum Sculpture, undated; 271485 (Box 80, Object ID: 386.2.0027)
- Series X: Library, 1931-2013; 6 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes.
  This series contains books, periodicals, exhibition catalogues, and other print material owned by Montano. Some print materials originally donated by Montano were removed during processing and are searchable via the library catalog.
  - Allsopp, Ric and deLahunta, Scott (Eds.). The connected body?: an interdisciplinary approach to the body and performance. Amsterdam: Amsterdam School of the Arts, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Antim, Eleanor. Being Antinova. Los Angeles: Astro Artz, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Atkins, Robert. ArtSpeak: a guide to contemporary ideas, movements, and buzzwords. New York: Abbeville Press Publishers, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Baas, Jacquelynn and Jacob, Mary Jane. Buddha mind in contemporary art. Berkeley: University of California Press, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Baker, Jo-Anne (Ed.). Sex tips & tales from Women Who Dare. Alameda, CA; Hunter House, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Jo-Anne (Ed.). Sex tips: advice from women experts around the world. Australia: Allen & Unwin, 1999 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Belloq, E.J. Storyville portraits; photographs from the New Orleans red-light district, circa 1912. New York: Museum of Modern Art; distributed by New York Graphic Society, Greenwich, CT, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Bloch, Ricardo and Celender, Don. Mortal Remains. New York: OK Harris Gallery, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Breitwieser, Sabine (Ed.). Double Life: Identity And Transformation In Contemporary Art. Wien: Generali Foundation, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Bucci, Mario. Giotto. New York: Grosset & Dunlap, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Carr, C. On edge: performance at the end of the twentieth century. Hanover, NH: Wesleyan University Press, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art. Outside the Frame: Performance and the Object. Cleveland, OH: Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art, 1994 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Craighead, Meinrad. The mother's songs: images of God the mother. New York: Paulist Press, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Crowne, Melchia. Sky cycle/Earth ring, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 14)